maxxdownload.com 2014-02-09

# MaxxDownload.com Privacy Policy

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers, we use log files.  These include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp to analyze trends, administer the site and track user’s movement in the aggregate.  IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. From time to time, we may ask users to provide an e-mail address or mailing address for the purpose of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters). Whenever the identity of a visitor is recorded, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the request before the information is requested. 

**Cookies**  
MaxxDownload may use cookies to ease storing and tracking your preferences.   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.   
MaxxDownload allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the MaxxDownload Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the MaxxDownload Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.  
MaxxDownload does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

**Security**  
This Website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked or open, when users are just "surfing".

**Links  
**This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we MaxxDownload.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us [here](http://www.maxxdownload.com/contact.html).
